<Mod>
  <ID>260dd8f3-537a-4d34-b3d5-956cda71eaca</ID>
  <Name>[Tsunamods] FF8 Gameplay Customizer</Name>
  <Author>Hobbitdu</Author>
  <Category>Gameplay</Category>
     <Description>
            &#9658; The ultimate gameplay tweaks &#9668;

This mods aims to bring lots of options to the gameplay to enjot your game how you want it !

    &#9670; General option &#9668;
        &#8226; Language: Only used for gerogero.

    &#9670; Game fix &#9668;
        &#8226; BahamutRareItem: Now actually increase the probability of really rare item.
        &#8226; GerogeroUncensoredMenu: Use the japanese version without color change.
        &#8226; GerogeroUncensoredBattle: Use the japanese version without color change.
        &#8226; TrueRandomness: Use a real random generator.
        &#8226; SquallComputeHit: Make squall fail sometimes !

    &#9670; Quality of life &#9668;
        &#8226; DamageCap: All damage can deal up to 65.535 (Eden damage is also cap to 65.535).
        &#8226; NoMagicDepletion: Using magic doesn't decrease your stock.
        &#8226; AP: Earn more AP after battle. Thanks to Satan-fatalityz for funding this !
        &#8226; XP: Earn more XP after battle. Thanks to Satan-fatalityz for funding this !
        &#8226; SaveAnywhere: To be able to save in field. Use at your own risk !
        &#8226; DrawRework: Change the draw logic (Either draw more than 9 or draw 100)

    &#9670; Little gameplay mod &#9668;
        &#8226; TripleTryhard: Card values changed for a challenge.
        &#8226; QueenForest: Queen of cards and Chocobo forest updated to be more convenient.

    &#9670; DifficultyBalance &#9668;
        &#8226; LimitbreakNotRefreshable: Make it impossible to refresh to get your limit-break.
        &#8226; NoGfHeal: No free heal on GF on hotel or by walking?
        &#8226; DamageFormulaUpdate: Change damage formula to have a smoother progression. Don't divide magic monster damage by 2.
        &#8226; JunctionRework: Junction value is linked to level or min between the level and the number of magic junctionned.
        &#8226; 255HitCanFail: Make that weapon can fail even at 255%.

    &#9670; Dev setup &#9668;
        &#8226; AddRandomVar: Allow modders to use random numbers in the AI.
        &#8226; SetAddr4: Allow modders to set any value in the game.
        &#8226; SetAddr1: Allow modders to set any value in the game.

    &#9670; Special thanks &#9668;
        &#8226; myst6re for Deling tool and RE work
        &#8226; Nihil for AI, stat, encounter rework
        &#8226; Malekith for stat rework
        &#8226; Unicorngoulash for LimitBreakNotRefreshable
        &#8226; AxlRoses for the awesome preview
        &#8226; Maki for his work on RE
        &#8226; Dulca for TripleTryHard and QueenForest
        &#8226; DangerousDom for beta testing

        Join the team or follow the news by clicking on the link ! Help me to continue this work participating in the Patreon page !

        Dev note - This mod use the following cave code:
        0x45B38C, 0x4670DC, 0x462605, 0x4626F9, 0x463090
    </Description>
  <LatestVersion>
    <Link>iroj://Url/https$modcdn.win/Hobbitdur/ff8_gameplay_customizer.zip</Link>
    <Version>0.7</Version>
      <ReleaseDate>2025-11-25</ReleaseDate>
    <CompatibleGameVersions>All</CompatibleGameVersions>
    <PreviewImage>https://modcdn.win/Hobbitdur/customizer_preview.png</PreviewImage>
    <ReleaseNotes>
    &#8226; 0.1
        Adding MaximumDraw, DamageCap, NoMagicDepletion
    &#8226; 0.2
        Adding 255AP, SaveAnywhere, BahamutRareItem, GerogeroUncensored, NoUnequippedOnDream, NoXP
    &#8226; 0.3
        Fixing SaveAnywhere
    &#8226; 0.4
        Adding DamageFormulaUpdate, LimitbreakNotRefreshable, JunctionDependOfLevel, JunctionDependOfMinLevelQuantity, TrueRandomness, G-Soldier
    &#8226; 0.5
        Change DamageFormulaUpdate, DrawNotLimited
    &#8226; 0.6
        Adding AiRework, QueenForest , TripleTryhard, SquallComputeHit, 255HitCanFail, GerogeroUncensoredMenu, GerogeroUncensoredBattle
               DrawPoint, FieldRework, MngrpRework, ShopRework, WIP, MonsterRework/Balanced
        Fixing SaveAnywhere
    &#8226; 0.7:
        Fix worldmap draw by changing SquallComputeHit, fix DrawRework/Draw100, fix encounter in forest
        Remove NoUnequippedOnDream (Creates bug when switching GF).
    &#8226; 0.8:
		Independent mod ! Adding XP and AP multiplier.
    </ReleaseNotes>
   <DownloadSize>2110</DownloadSize>
  </LatestVersion>
  <Link>https://discord.gg/A7uFA4WqQY</Link>
  <DonationLink>https://www.patreon.com/c/HobbitMods</DonationLink>
  <Tags>
    <string>cronos</string>
    <string>ff8</string>
    <string>customizer</string>
    <string>hard</string>
    <string>mod</string>
    <string>gameplay</string>
    <string>hobbit</string>
    <string>hobbitdur</string>
  </Tags>
</Mod>
